<resources>
    <string name="app_name">EwuHub</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="sort_course_description">Please, Input total number of subjects you want to sort for advising.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sort_course_home">Sort Courses</string>
    <string name="title_activity_course_input">Sort Courses</string>
    <string name="course_input_description">Please, Input name of the subjects you want to sort.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_show_sort_courses">Sort Courses</string>
    <string name="title_activity_course_details">Subject Details</string>
    <string name="ewu_history">The idea of establishing a private university
        to provide quality education at an affordable cost in Bangladesh was
        first mooted by a group of prominent academics, business leaders, professionals
        and education enthusiasts led by Dr. Mohammed Farashuddin. With this end in view,
        this group formed a non-profit, non-political, charitable organization called Progoti
        Foundation for Education and Development (PFED). East West University is its first major
        project. Members of the Board of Directors of the University are: Mr. Jalaluddin Ahmed,
        Mr. S.M. Nousher Ali, Mr. Farooque B. Chaudhury, Dr. Rafiqul Huda Chaudhury,
        Mr. Syed Manzur Elahi, Dr. Mohammed Farashuddin, Mr. Mohammed Zahidul Haque R.Ph.,
        Dr. Saidur Rahman Lasker, Dr. Muhammad A. Mannan, Professor M. Mosleh-Uddin, Mr. Shelley
        A. Mubdi, Mr. M.A. Mumin, Dr. Khalil Rahman, Mr. H.N. Ashequr Rahman and Mrs. Razia
        Samad. After being accorded permission by the Government under the Private University
        Act (Act 34) of 1992, East West University was launched in 1996. Classes started in
        September 1996 with 6 faculty members and 20 students in the campus located at 43
        Mohakhali C/A, Dhaka-1212. Today there are over 281 faculty members and approximately
        8000 students enrolled through a process of selection.</string>

    <string name="ewu_mission_statement">In keeping with its name, East West University, rated
        among the top private universities of Bangladesh, is an institution that promotes
        eastern culture and values, and meaningfully blends eastern and western thought and
        innovation. As an institution of higher learning that promotes and inculcates ethical
        standards, values and norms, East West University (EWU) is committed to the ideals of
        equal opportunity, transparency, and non-discrimination. The primary mission of EWU is
        to provide, at a reasonable cost, tertiary education characterized by academic
        excellence in a range of subjects that are particularly relevant to current and
        anticipated societal needs. Central to the university’s mission is its intention to
        provide students with opportunities, resources and expertise to achieve academic,
        personal and career goals within a stimulating and supportive environment. EWU is
        striving not only to maintain high quality in both instruction and research, it is
        also rendering community service through dissemination of information, organization
        of training programs and other activities. Sensitive to the needs of its students and
        staff, EWU is committed to providing a humane, responsive and invigorating atmosphere
        for productive learning and innovative thinking.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_ewu_spirit">Ewu Spirit</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_academic_calendar">Academic Calendar</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="undergraduate"></string>
    <string name="title_activity_notice">Notice Board</string>
    <string name="title_activity_notice_web_viewer">Notice Viewer</string>
</resources>
